GABRIEL KUETTEL EULL STACK WER DEVELOPER & DESIGNER



Full Stack Web Developer with a knack for designing and developing robust and user-friendly interfaces and websites using modern frameworks and build tools, including React, Angular, Node/Express (MERN/MEAN), GraphQL, Gatsby/Hugo/Jekyll, MongoDB and MySQL. Background in graphic design, with four years experience in UX/UI, branding, and motion design.

EXPERIENCE

GK DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

Boulder, CO, USA

April 2019 - August 2019

HOUSING DATA SYSTEMS - CONTRACT

Designed UX/UI and developed Dashboard system in Angular, consumed REST services to dynamically generate reports, interactive tables and data visualizations.

Developed frontend for reporting center in Angular, used by housing managers to access reports, visualizations, and raw data.

Worked with agile team to deliver features, enhancements and bug fixes in an AngularJS application.

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

Denver, CO, USA

March 2019 - August 2019

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP TEACHING ASSISTANT

Guided students in learning HTML/CSS/JavaScript, React, Node/Express, MySQL, MongoDB in a classroom setting and one-on-one teaching sessions.

Tackled a variety of challenges and assisted students in developing projects, debugging code, git collaboration and deployment.

Graded projects and assignments and lead group review sessions.

GOLD STANDARD

Geneva, Switzerland

April 2016 - November 2018

MULTIMEDIA OFFICER

Designed and created the Project Developer Portal, a purpose-built LAMP/Wordpress portal for technical documentation, training videos, and additional resources used by 1,700 climate projects.

UX/UI design for the Gold Standard Platform, an online collaborative platform for news and discussion used by NGOs and key partners.

Designed and developed landing pages for events, marketing initiatives, and climate projects, using HTML/CSS/JavaScript and Adobe Creative Suite.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

- > HTML / CSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript / JQuery

FRONTEND TECHNOLOGIES

- React / Angular / AngularJS
- Gatsby / Hugo / Jekyll

BACKEND TECHNOLOGIES

Node / Express

DATABASES

- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Firebase

VERSIONING & OTHER TOOLS

- Git / Jira / Linux / Command Line
 - DESIGN
- UX / UI
- Branding
- Motion Design

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER, DENVER, CO

July 2018 - January 2019

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node/Express, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku deployment, Git
- Capstone project: GitCamp, a project collaboration platform built with the Github API, using React, Node/Express and MongoDB

UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO, BOULDER, CO

August 2010 - August 2014

BACHELOR'S IN INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS

> Emphasis: Middle East geopolitics, Farsi language